A Guide to the Records of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, Extradition Requisition and Rendition Files of Governor Robert F. McDonnell, 2010-2013
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Extraditions Requisitions and Renditions: Requisitions, 2010-2013., Extent: 8 cu. ft. (8 boxes) (Box Boxes 5-12)
  - Dowery, Thomas Allen, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Eberhard, Jeremy Michael, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Edge, Janet Little, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Edwards, Shirleen, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Eli, Kevin C., 2010 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Fernald, Adam Ray, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Finney, Lashaunda Tawana, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Fortune, Gloria Lenette, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Gardiner, Shave Giovanni, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Garris, Marvin Ronald, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Garrison, Robert Louis, II, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Gayle, Michael Craig, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Gates, Tammie K., 2010 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Goins, Zachary Vanquail, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Golden, Stephanie, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Graybeal, Davis, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Gregory, Crystal Gail, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Greenwood, James Donald, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Griffin, Wilton Christopher, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Guest, John B., 2010 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Haigler, Christopher Eugene, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Hall, Richard Ernest, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Hammond, Vincent Bernard, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Hampton, Alexandria Tammy, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Hanks, Damond Lee, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Harbison, Michael Ryan, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Harris, Irving Lonniel, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Harvey, Carolyn Denise, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - Hasty, Alvin Mitchell, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Hatton, Jonathan Paul, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Hendrix, Carl, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Hernandez, Benito Miranda, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Hodges, Kevin Keith, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Huelle, Mark, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Jackson, Derrick, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Jackson, Khalid Jamal, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Jacobs, Billy, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Johnson, Carver George, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Johnson, Lavonzelle Lavette, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Jones, Joshua Marlin, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - King, Larry Dwayne, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Kirby, Julie, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Klopp, Jeffrey, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Knight, Albert Cyrus, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Lafontant, Patrick, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Langwig, Frank R., V, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Larson, Kristan Amanda, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Lawrance, Larry William, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Lewis, Antonio Palysia, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Lewis, Nicholas Alexander, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Light, Franklin Curtis, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Lohrey, Sandra C., 2010 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Long, Donald James, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Luciano, Tealeye, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Macnell, Patrick F., 2010 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Nicholson, Lavernal Teon, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Norman, Brian, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Marino, Jonathan Ward, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Marquette, Thomas Stephen, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Martin, Melissa Marie, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Martin, Patricia Ann, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - McBride, Reginald, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - McKenzie, Salim, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - McLaughlin, Frederick Wayne, Jr., 2010 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - McLain, Shawn Lee, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Melvin, Randy Eugene, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Mickleberry, DeAndre, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Mills, Ashley Laroy, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Miller, Perry Allen, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Montgomery, Richard Wayne, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Morales-Sanchez, Daniel, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Moser, Sharon Denise, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Mullens, Roger Glen, Jr., 2010 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Nava-Media, Martin, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Nichols, Uneeda T., 2010 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Norris, Irvin Thomas, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - O'Conner, Sean Edwards, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Ongombe, Patrick Victor, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Ortiz, Kimberly, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Parker-Nathan, Gloria Cecilia, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Parks, Marcus Lamont, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Perkins, Francis Ilene, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Pethoud, John Brenton, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Poff, William Christopher, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Poston, Christopher, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Pratt, Earl Ivan, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Price, Kimberly Marie, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Propst, Todd Anthony, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Ramirez, Matthew, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Ramsey, David, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Reagan, Daniel Theodore, II, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Reid, Sandra Ann, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Riley, Sarah Rose, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Robinson, Dawn Sherie, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Robinson, Martha Madeline, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Rodgers, Terrence Ira, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Rowell, Leander Bruce, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Russ, Debony D., 2010 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Sanchez, Ricardo Octavio, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Sanders, Ronald Webster, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Saunders, Marvin Lewis, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Scott, Rene Diane, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Simpson, Eunice Cristina, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Simpson, Michael Kentell, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Slonaker, Juliet L., 2010 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Smith, Lainder Randall, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Southern, Dylan Troy, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Soyars, Mary Ann, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Spencer, Tinamarie, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Stewart, Christopher Maurice, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Stokes, Sherial Laron, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Suarez, Daniel A. Rosa, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Taylor, Charles Lee, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Taylor, Christopher Graham, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Taylor, Desiree Gloria, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Taylor, Travis Eugene, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Taylor, Willie Lee, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Terry, Joshua Michael, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Trevena, Charles Thomas, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Upchurch, John Andre, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Vaughn, Donald Doc, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Vaughn, William Mark, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Versher, Dale Patrick, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Vick, Lewis Lovskly, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Walden, William, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Walton, Kevin, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Watlington, Jason Jerome, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Whissel, Mark, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - White, Lonnie Edward, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Whitlow, Joseph Allen, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Wiggins, John Reed, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Williams, Anthony, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - Williams, Christopher Gerald, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Willis, Eddie, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Wilson, Kyle Christopher, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Wright, Charlie, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Wright, Dawn, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Wright, Keith Douglas, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Wright, Tracy, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Wright, Anthony Gregory, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Acosta, Jose Adiel, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Adamou, Idrissa, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Alexander, Brian Nicholas, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Alfaro, Miguel Angel, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Allman, Ronald H., II, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Alston, Kian Deric, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Anderson, Cort William, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Applegate, Jacqueline Marie, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Arroyo, Michael Joel, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Arthur, Paul Eugene, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Askew, Robert C., III, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Ayers, April Dawn, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Barrow, John Franklin, Jr., 2011 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Bartley, Michael, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Bays, Casey Gene, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Beitler, Joseph Franklin, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Bell, Justin Troy, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Benevento, Andrew Blaine, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Best, Montana Antwain, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Best, Robert Davon, Jr., 2011 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Blankenship, Dorsel Brian, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Bogle, Scottie Ray, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Booker, James Seth, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Briel, William Barney, Jr., 2011 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Bright, Joshua Arlington, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Brown, Philshawn Carlos, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Bunch, Desirea L., 2011 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Burdette, Amy Press, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Burgess, Levi, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Burnham, Clifton Alexander, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Byrd, Emmitte Carl, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Byrd, Michael Antuan, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Byrne, James John, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Caban, Jose Hector, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Caraballo, Juan, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Carpenter, Marsha G., 2011 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Cates, Terry Cornelius, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Chand, Venus Vishal, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Cherry, Dominique Deon, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Cherry, Eric Paul, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Chumley, Carl Brian, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Clay, Gene Autry, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Clifton, Leslie, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Crater, Jerry Michael, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Crovell, Xavier, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Dashnaw, Christopher Matthew, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Dela Mora, Everado George, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Deloatch, Karen, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Depace, Daniel Edward, III, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Deparasis, Jennifer Marie, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Edwards, Brian Lee, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - El-Amin, Tariq Abdul, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Elliot, Deshara Kayavon, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Escalon-Murillo, Evelin Jakeline, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Faulkner, Deema Nicole, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Felton, Felicia Lafaye, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Ford, Sebastian Brake, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Gamble, Anthony, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Gantt, Daniel Wayne, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Gray, Clifton Eugene, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Green, Jamar Dominic, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Gwynn, Mitchell L., 2011 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Hall, Clarence Eugene, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Hampton, Donte D., 2011 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Harden, Marion, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Hargrove, Derrick Lamont, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Harper, Alfred Allen, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Harrison, Jerry Jerome, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Harrison, Venus Camille, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Hartwell, Ronald Lee, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Hawks, Eric Darrell, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Helmick, Matthew Patrick, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Henderson, Shamir Darnell, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Hill, Levi Daniel, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Holloway, Diane Renee, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Hoskins, Frederick Thomas, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Huett, Shelly Ann, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Hutchinson, Anthony Barrington, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Ingram, Mark Wayne, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Johnston, Alison, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Johnson, Djavon Khalil, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Jones, Antwain Maurice, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Jones, Wallace David Lamont, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Keeylan, Kenneth Eugene, III, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Kelley, David Allen, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Kinard, Michael Dwayne, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - King, Jeromie Keith, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Kirk, Lowell Edward, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Lamberth, Janice Rebecca, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Lipscomb, Timothy Lewis, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Looney, Christopher Marsee, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Lupton, Michael Travis, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Marks, Melissa Maria, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Martin, Richard Wayne, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Martin, William Charles, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - McBride, Michael Lamont, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - McCullers, Antoine Demetrius, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Mejia, Edgar A., 2011 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Miller, Shaun Thomas, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Milton, Edwin Lewis, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Mintz, Michael Allen, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Mitchell, Kenneth, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Monson, Keri Ann, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Moyer, William Lee, Jr., 2011 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Murphy, Beverly Jean, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Murphy, Darrin William, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Nelson, Robert Lee, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Nguyen, Ty Van, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Nimmons, Lakesha, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Norman, Jeraldine M., 2011 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Olaniyan, Adeola Modupe, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Owens, Tommy, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Pannell, Sonmer La-Ruesh, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Pannell, Sonmer La-Ruesh, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Parker, Charles Lanis, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Pendergrass, Antonio Domonique, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Pennix, Amanda, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Petitford, Todd Maurica, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Phillips, Michael Lee, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Pineda, Juan Miguel, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Powens, Charlie, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Pratt, Earl Ivan, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Procida, William James, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Pruitt, Crystal Leigh, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Ragin, John Moses, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Reed, Angela Lee, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Repass, William Scott, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Reyes, Jose Walter, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Roberts, Charles Mark, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Roudabush, James Lester, Jr., 2011 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Royal, Anthony A., 2011 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Rubio, Juan Jose, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Ruelas, Noel Leon, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Rumley, Ronald David, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Saunders, Jeffrey Matthew, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Saunders, Ryan Scott, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Schmidt, Karin Leslie, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Scott, Jack Allen, II, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Shonyo, Elizabeth Ann, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Skaggs, William Gerald, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Smith, Joshua Shawn, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Smith, Lauren King, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Sowell, Sharell Yolanda, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Stotts, Christopher D., 2011 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Strader, Jimmy Dean, Jr., 2011 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Sturdivant, Steven Chea, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Swinford, Kristine A., 2011 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Takpara, Ayewa Essofa, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Taylor, Colin Michael, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Terroni, Catherine Jean, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Thomas, Aaron, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Thompson, Edward Lee, IV, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Todd, David Anthony, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Tolliver, Misti Dawn, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Trevena, Charles Thomas, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Twerefour, Richard, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Underwood, William Michael, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Valentine, Thomas E., Jr., 2011 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Vasquez, Miguel Ortiz, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Walden, Cynthia Jean, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Warlick, Shannon R., 2011 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Waggy, Michael Scott, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Warring, Tyresse Ocemia, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Watts, Kevin Phillip, Jr., 2011 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Welch, Ronald, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - White, Jackie Lynn, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Williams, Don Jerome, Jr., 2011 (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Williams, Michael Todd, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Williams, Yelondo Jerodis, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Wills, Lauren Ashley, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 78)
  - Winn, Nicholas Brandon, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - Winnett, Kenneth D., 2011 (Box 8, Folder 80)
  - Winstead, Larry, Jr., 2011 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Wright, Natilda, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Young, Jason Matthew, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - Young, Stephen Douglas, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Adams, Cordaro Eugene, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Adams, James Franklin, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Adams, Dwayne, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Adams, James Franklin, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Adams, James Franklin, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Airtrip, Jeffrey Adam, Jr., 2012 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Ali, Khalid Mohammad, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Anderson, Terry R., 2012 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Arrington, Eric Jason, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Bagget, Daniel, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Bagwell, Jonathan James, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Bangura, Amadu, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Bannister, Sean Carson Leroy, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Barlow, Kenneth Lee, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Barrett, Shane Michael, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Bea, Maximilian Anthony, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Bee, Jack Allan, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Belza, Steven James, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Bernard, Chazz Deangelo Dyer, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Bethel, Raymond, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Bishop, Kenneth Ruben, Jr., 2012 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Blakely, Devon 2012 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Blankenship, Renee Misty, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Brame, Christopher Demite, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Bray, Jacues Wiley, Jr., 2012 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Brooker, Monica Hollis, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Brown, Larry Wayne, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Brown, Ronald Dale, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Bryce, James Wallace, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Butler, Demarcus Terrell, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Byars, Jenny Dawn, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Calhoun, Joseph Michael, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Calloway, Rodney F., 2012 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Campbell, Jessica, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Clipse, Joey Dale, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Coker, Houston Alexander, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Cole, Amanda Brooke, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Collins, Jonathan Martin, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Collins, Richard Allen, Jr., 2012 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Cooper, Letisha Michele, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Corley, Angus, Jr., 2012 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Crawley, Bryan Owen, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Creskoff, Heather M., 2012 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Cumming, Tommi Suzannah, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - D'Amato, Janelle Nicole, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Dail, Joshua Brandan, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Davis, Cimone Danielle, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Davis, Derrek Allan, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Davis, Richard, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Davis, Valerie Denise, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Daye, James Herefore, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Dickerson, Khalil, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Dodgson, Charles, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Douglas, Justin S., 2012 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Douglas, Shavon Unique, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Drummer, Derek Alan, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Dudley, Robert Edward, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Dugais, Edsel Deshon, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Ester, James Corey, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Farmer, Desmond A., 2012 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Fisher, Richard Dale, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Fortenberry, Peter John, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Foster, Michael Lee, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Gaines, Richard Thomas, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Gary, Stephen Michael, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Geiser, Arthur Edward, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Gerald, Marcell Jonte, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Goodings, Brian K., 2012 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Goodman, Brian Lee, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Gorman, John Kevin, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - Greene, Karen D., 2012 (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Grocan, Rachelle Simms, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 71)
  - Hackley, Yvonne Evette, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 72)
  - Hagan, Gregory, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 73)
  - Hairston, Irvin Eugene, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - Hairston, Michael Shannon, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Hall, Danta Jamar, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Hamilton, Tyler Lee, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Harden, Michael A., 2012 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Hardy, Benjamin, Jr., 2012 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Harris, Jay Steven, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Hawks, Randy Dean, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Hayes, Anthony Allen, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Henley, Alfred William, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Herron, Jayson M., 2012 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Hess, Roger Wayne, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Hoke, Troy Douglas, et al., 2012 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Holder, Henry Joseph Harper, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Holloway, Diane Renee, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Hubbard, Ashton Denise, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Ingram, Mark Wayne, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Ishmael, Munner Y., 2012 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Jarvis, Thomas Ray, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Jenkins, Nicholas Nelson, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, Angelise Michelle, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Jones, Julian Devon, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Jones, Mark Allen, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Jordan, George, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Journigan, Samantha Lynn, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Joy, Ricky Wayne, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Kearns, Michael Thomas, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Keith, Timothy Lewis, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Keith, Timothy Lewis, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Kincer, Bennet Matthew, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Knox, David Reid, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Lanson, Nancy Anita, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Larocque, Rudolph Phillippe, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Lawson, Dustin Neil, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Lester, Estel Lee, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Lewis, Joshua Phillip, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Loftin, Denzil A., 2012 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Long, Anthony Houston, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Lopez, Joseph Thomas-Lee, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Luhrson, Robert John, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Manock, Jon Ellis, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Marsh, Fiona Elizabeth, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Mburu, Kunga, (aka Gakunga Brown) 2012 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - McCaden, Bobby A., 2012 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - McKoy, Shaun Martez, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - McFarland, Jody Adrianne, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - McLean, Leonard Warren, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - McNair, Timothy Wayne, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Medina, Joshue, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Meyers, Conforti Latanya, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Miller, Sharon Cromedi, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Miller, Tyrell, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Mullins, John Wayne, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Moore, Paul Wayne, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Myers, John Edward, II, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Newman, Gregory Wendell, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Nunez, Laika J., 2012 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Nunnally, Preston Shaquante, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Ortiz, Javier Hernandez, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Ortiz, Javier Hernandez, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Painter, Keith Onslow, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Palacios, Jorge, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Pankey, Stafford Lee, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Parker, Charles Lanis, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Perry, Torrey Wayne, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Porter, Courtney L., 2012 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Powell, Bedford Carroll, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Pride, Jonathan Blake, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Przybkski, Rachelle Anne, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Rainey, Rowland Jeffery, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Ramseur, Antonio Garfield, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Reid, Lawrence, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Rhodes, Michael Paul, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Richardson, Virgil Lee, Jr., 2012 (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Riel, Jeffrey Douglas, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Ring, James Calvin, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Rosenberg, Lavonda Denise, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - Royster, Kevin Homer, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Schneeburger, Nicholas, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Schendel, Trevor Xavier, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 63)